Razboynikov Pavel

Buenos Aires, Argentine • +347-4359-4547 • mansiper@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/razboynik/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I have 16 years of total experience. Including 8.5 years as a C# developer and 3 years as a Go developer, focusing on back-end engineering with .NET Core and Go. I also utilize Blazor and React.js for the front-end. Successfully automatized overr 20 factories, developed successful service for pharmacy market from scratch, designed DB architecture for different services, worked on some startup and open-source projects.

I work on each project as if it were my own, always trying to find a way to make it better.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Engineer

Jun 2024 – present

Outlines Tech

An outstaff developer for the back-office of a building construction company

Successfully rid off the technical debt, covered code with tests, fixed existing and potential bugs.

Create new and update old microservices for a construction company. Maintain service operations across all environments.

.NET Core, EF, REST API, gRPC, CQRS, Kafka, PostgreSQL, Grafana, GitLab, Jira

Senior Software Engineer Self-Employeed, Remote

Apr 2023 – Jun 2024

A website for dancers worldwide: https://iwd.today

Utilized Trello for efficient self-management, saving user stories, overseeing tasks, prioritizing activities. All developed by myself with a little graphic designer assistance.

Back-end: .NET Core, EF, MS SQL, RestAPI. Front-end: Blazor, Bootstrap, JS (jQuery).

A website for the gym statistics: https://gymstats.info/watch (read-only mode)

With Blazor only it works pretty slow, thus I'm changing it to Go+React+MongoDB

Telegram-bot for saving shopping list, daily tasks, and calendar events.

Wrote in C# with the integration of the ChatGPT API for recognizing user's text and voice messages.

Senior Software Engineer

Jul 2022 - Oct 2023

EPAM Systems, Yerevan, Armenia

A webservice for real estate information and document management

Successfully developed new integration services with various third-party companies. Then started working on the main service. Added new features, improved existing code, fixed bugs, generated new ideas for a better user experience. .NET Core, WCF, Dapper, NUnit, SQL, RESTful service, Azure, Swagger

Senior back-end developer Intspirit, Moscow, Russia

Jan 2021 - Jun 2022

An outstaff developer for one of the biggest banks in Russia, back-end for mobile app's stock exchange module Developed new microservices, worked on refactoring and enhancement of existing ones. I was responsible for identifying and mitigating vulnerabilities within the service architecture, collaborating with the security team, managing team tasks for solving these problems. I created new tasks, analyzed time, controlled task performance.

.NET Core, MSSQL, Dapper, NUnit, Kafka, SQL

Back-end developer

Feb 2018 – Dec 2020

SKB Kontur, Yekaterinburg, Russia

Services for online accounting and business

Developed "Vostok" (https://github.com/Vostok), an open-source project (worked on logging and configuration libraries). I tested new universal "data pipe" ("Hercules") for the global monitoring (logging and metrics) of all company services. I improved inner document-oriented DB ("Zebra") adding SQL-like language support. While working on the "Factoring" project, significantly reduced errors and enhanced system reliability. Created ETL services for the transferring ML-generated data between Kafka storages. Set up TeamCity pipelines. Tried to implement an idea of creating new startup project within the company for the pharmacy market. Used CustDev for market researching. Recorded a lecture for colleagues about Regular Expressions.

.NET Framework 4.5 - .NET Core 3, .NET Standard 2.0, xUnit, NUnit, EF, React, MSSQL, Kafka, Cassandra, Kibana, Grafana, TeamCity, GitHub

Full-stack developer

Jul 2017 – Apr 2018

Freelancer, Yekaterinburg, Russia

A website for storing and sharing business contacts.

Designed and developed DB architecture and back-end REST API from scratch Connected internet acquiring for receiving user payments.

.NET Framework 4.6, MVC, NHibernate, NUnit, MvSOL

Senior developer Aug 2016 – Jul 2017

Business Partner Ltd., Yekaterinburg, Russia

An aggregator of private bus transportation, back-office services

Significantly enhanced performance across projects by optimizing SQL queries.

Improved WinForm application integration with Asterisk for the call center, made it faster and more user-friendly.

Researched and worked on architecture modernization by starting seamless migration process from WebForms to MVC. Developed a Golang service for Linux for call record sharing from the MVC project page.

Created a browser extension (JS + Golang) for real-time service monitoring. This instrument helped identify and resolve a critical database issue.

Conducted training sessions for colleagues on writing optimized SQL queries and effectively utilizing ORM.

Worked on migration process from the local server to Azure, enhancing system reliability.

.NET Framework 4.6, NHibernate, NUnit, Golang, Telerik, JavaScript, WinForms, WebForms, MVC, Asterisk

Director and ICS developer

Oct 2008- Dec 2016

SKB SUIK LLC., Yekaterinburg, Russia

Factories automation, for hardware

As a developer, created numerous applications from the ground up, specializing in hardware integration for diverse industrial environments: manufacturing line operators, programmable logic controllers, data collection, etc.

Full system control, processes monitoring, documents preparation, full product support. Successful equipment and software integration. Developed PLC emulator for applications testing.

As a director, managed contract negotiations and signings.

Successfully executed around 20 projects for factory automation across various industries, including asphalt, concrete, cement production, cat litter bags counting, glue production via PLC, and an experimental separator for nuclear materials. Turnkey development (hardware, electronics, software).

Delphi, CoDeSys, Golang, Firebird, MySQL, Fast Report, DevExpress, Modbus-RTU, OOo Calc API and MS Excel API, Raspberry Pi

EDUCATION

Ural State Technical University, Yekaterinburg, Russia Engineer's degree, 2013

SKILLS

C#, Go, ReactJS, JS, .NET Core, Blazor, EF, REST API, gRPC, MSSQL, MySQL, MongoDB, Nunit

LANGUAGES

English (B2), Spanish (A2), Russian (native)